New York State Division of Human Rights Decisions 5882
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Division of Human Rights Decisions
1989-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Division of Human Rights
5882
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Reports (documents).
5725200
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 22, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6047: Archives Information File
Discrimination--New York (State); New York (State). State Division of Human Rights.
5725200
- Arthur C. Bailey vs. Raymond Liebesman and Company, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Case no. 1A-E-D-110575
- Sarah Baruch vs. Ramapo Helicopters, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Case no. 3E-CN-86-114697-E
- Vernita Y. Bing vs. Quality Care, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Case no. 5-E-R-97355-84E
- Julia Burgess vs. Family Hairstylists, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Case no. 3-E-S-84-95489
- Julia M. Dethier vs. Ecological Society of America, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Case nos. 9E-E-MS-5206-79 and 9E-E-MS-62088-79
- Joseph F. Farley vs. New York State Department of Civil Service, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Case no. 5-E-D-91765-83
- Joseph M. Haaf vs. Holmes Protection, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Case no. 1B-E-A-84-100718A
- Robert M. Haley, Jr. vs. Syracuse University, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Case no. 9E-E-A-49192-77
- Douglas W. Hewitt vs. New York State Department of Correctional Services, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Case no. 5-E-D-85-105513
- Horace Jenkins vs. Lyell Metal Company, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Case no. 6-E-R-85-106077E
- Johnny Johnson vs. City of New York, NY, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Case no. 1A-E-86-113655
- Vivian L. May vs. NASCO North American, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Case no. 1A-E-R-84-99285E
- Raymond L. Morin vs. General Electric, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Case no. 1B-E-A-93365-83A
- Salvatore A. Paonessa vs. City of Niagara Falls, NY and Gary M. Hayes vs. City of Niagara Falls, NY, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Case nos. 7-E-D-82277-82 and 7-E-D- 102639-85
- Joseph Porcello vs. General Motors, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Case no. 3-E-D-85-103994
- Ruth Rivera vs. Home Attendants Program, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Case nos. 1B-E-O-95439-84 and 1B-E-RNS-93844-84E
- Mary Winch vs. Grumman Aerospace, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Case no. 2A-E-OS-84-99180E